regus.com 2018-10-09

# Privacy Policy | Regus US

## Information about our organization and websites

This Privacy Policy informs you of the privacy practices, the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online, how that information is used and the rights that you have if your use of this website falls under the jurisdiction of the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 ("GDPR"). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and revisit this page from time to time to review any changes that may have been made.

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect on the date set out in the posted Privacy Policy, unless otherwise specified.

## Sites covered by this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all our websites and domains including all regional or country-specific sites (collectively the “Websites”). The Websites may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the Websites. We do not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from our own privacy practices. This Privacy Policy does not cover any personal data that you choose to give to unrelated third parties. We do not monitor or control the information collected by such sites or the privacy practices of any third parties, and we are not responsible for their practices or the content of their sites.

## Types of information we collect and use

In this policy, “personal information” or “personal data” means information about an identifiable individual that is subject to protection under the law in the jurisdiction in which you reside. In some jurisdictions, “personal information” or “personal data” will not include business contact information.

The Websites collect information through a variety of different ways and for different purposes as follows. If you choose to register with any of the Websites to receive updates from us, to manage your account and/or use our self-service portal, then you will be requested to provide contact information (name, address, telephone number, email address, a unique login name and password). We use this information pursuant to our legitimate business interests to provide our services and/or to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

We may also use your contact information to send you information about other group products and services, such as meeting rooms, virtual offices, workplace recovery, offices, co-working and memberships subject to us having obtained your consent in accordance with the applicable laws. If you do not want to receive these promotional announcements on an on-going basis, you can notify us to update your preferences (see the Opt-Out section below).   
You also have the option to provide demographic information (such as type of business, size of business, locations, etc.). We use this demographic information to understand your needs and interests and to provide you a more personalized experience on our site. The information is used by the group to process your orders, enable participation in promotions (subject to your marketing preferences) and so that we can provide our services to you.

Through the Websites, you can order products or services, request information, or subscribe to marketing or support materials. In order to purchase a product or service from us, we will request certain information from you which will be used for contract performance purposes. You will need to provide contact information (such as your name, email and shipping address) and financial information (such as a credit card number, billing address and expiration date). Financial information collected from you is used only to bill you for the products and services that you have purchased.

If we collect credit card information from you, we only use this information for payment processing and fraud prevention. Credit card information and other similar sensitive personal data are not used for any other purpose by the group without your express consent. We do not retain your credit card information after processing a payment unless you grant us permission to retain your credit card information for future purchases.

The Websites automatically collect technical information about your visit (such as the browser type, internet service provider, platform type, internet protocol (IP) addresses, referring/exit pages, operating system and date/time stamp). We aggregate this information for reporting about the Websites to analyse trends, diagnose problems with our server and administer the Websites, to track user movement and use, and to gather broad demographic information. See "Cookies and other digital markers" below for more information.

We may be required to share information with third parties as a result of the applicable laws. For example, we may be required to disclose information as a result of a court order, subpoena or warrant. In addition, we may, subject to the applicable laws, voluntarily provide information in order to assist in a law enforcement investigation or where the disclosure is necessary to protect our systems, our business or the rights of others

## Communications 

Once you register, we will send you a welcome email to verify your username and password. We will also respond to your inquiries, provide services you request and manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone and will make every effort to honor your preference.

Subject to the marketing preferences which you give us, we will also send you information on new products, services, special savings, promotions and general information. If you do not want to receive this information, you can opt-out of receiving future mailings (see Opt-Out section below).

If you ask to subscribe to our newsletters, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. You can sign up for these newsletters from us on our registration page. You may unsubscribe at any time (see Opt-Out section below).

When necessary, we will send you service-related announcements, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you may deactivate your account with the Website.

Please note that we do not provide your email address to our business partners. However, we may send you offers on behalf of our business partners – see "Types of information we collect and use" above for more details. You can opt out from receiving email offers from us as described below.

## Sharing of information and Cross-border Transfers

We contract with third-party service providers and suppliers to deliver complete products, services and customer solutions described above. These service providers may change or we may contract with additional service providers to better accommodate our customers. Our affiliates may provide services to you or to your local affiliate and may receive personal data about you. If we transfer your personal data to affiliates or third parties, we require the recipients of your personal data to safeguard your personal data using administrative, technical and security procedures; however, your personal data will also be subject to the laws of the jurisdiction governing our affiliate or the third party.

Your personal data may be transferred across state borders and country borders to our affiliate companies in order to provide our services to you. Residents of the EEA and Canada should understand that your personal data may be transferred outside of the EEA and Canada to the United States and other countries for the purposes of data consolidation, storage, simplified customer information management, reporting and other internal uses. We have implemented EC-approved form model clauses to achieve compliance with EU data transfer laws.

## Cookies and other digital markers

We automatically gather information through the use of cookies and other digital markers. Cookies and digital markers are small computer files that may be stored on your computer’s hard drive or embedded in our website pages that enable us to identify you and track your visit on the Website. For example, when you book office space, we use cookies in the checkout process in order to keep track of your order as you move through each step of the booking process. We may use the services of third-parties to collect and process personal information through the use of cookies and other digital markers on our behalf. You may disable cookies on your computer by changing the settings in the preferences or options menu in your browser. If you choose to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas of the Website.

## Children’s privacy

The group is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. The group does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and we do not target its websites to children under 13.

## Your choices and opting-out

We give you the choice of receiving a variety of information that complements our products and services. You can subscribe to receive certain product-and service-specific information and group-wide marketing communications. Such communications may include new product information, special offers or an invitation to participate in market research.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters and/or promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communications including by contacting us at [crm.suppressions@regus.com](mailto:crm.suppressions@regus.com?Subject=Opt-Out)

## Access to and accuracy of your information and your other rights

In certain jurisdictions, notably the EU and the UK, you have a right: to ask us for a copy of your personal information; to ask us to correct, delete or restrict (stop any active) processing of your personal data and to obtain the personal data you provide to us for a contract or with your consent and to ask us to share (port) this data to another data controller; to object to the processing of your personal information by us in some circumstances (in particular, where we don't have to process the data to meet a contractual or other legal requirement or where we are using the data for direct marketing). These rights may be limited, for example, if fulfilling your request would reveal personal data about another person or breach the privacy rights of others, or if you ask us to delete information which we are required by law to keep or have compelling legitimate interests in keeping. To exercise any of these rights, please contact [gdpr@regus.com](mailto:gdpr@regus.com?Subject=). If you have unresolved concerns, you have the right to make a complaint to the data protection supervisory authority where you live, work or where you believe a breach may have occurred.

## Keeping your information secure

We do not guarantee or warrant the security of our servers nor can we guarantee that information you supply through the Website will not be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet. We follow generally accepted industry technical standards to protect the personal data submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card information) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secured socket layer technology.

Where we process personal information for marketing purposes or with your consent, we process the data until you ask us to stop and for a short period after this (to allow us to implement your requests). We also keep a record of the fact that you have asked us not to send you direct marketing or to process your data indefinitely so that we can respect your request in the future. Where we process personal information in connection with performing a contract or service, or for a competition, we keep the information for 6 years (except for financial information which we keep for 10 years) from your last interaction with us.

## Business transitions

In the event that we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred.

## Terms and Conditions

If you choose to visit our Websites, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, including, but not limited to, disclaimers of warranty, limitations of liability, and arbitration of disputes. If you have any questions regarding our use of your data, please email [gdpr@regus.com](mailto:gdpr@regus.com?Subject=)

April 2018
